passion4fm.com 2016-06-08

# Passion4FM Privacy Policy | Passion4FM

## The Privacy policy below describes how Passion4FM.com collects and use the information about its website visitors (You and/or The Website Users)

LAST UPDATED 09. SEPTEMBER 2015 

We at Passion4FM.com have created this privacy statement in order to show my commitment to my and your privacy. This page explains our approach to privacy and our practices to gather informations from you as visitor at www.Passion4FM.com (hereinafter referred to as: the “Website”), and finally how the information gathering and dissemination practices affects you. Our privacy policy page guides you through how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us, and how you for any reason should disable the use of cookies at the website. This Privacy Policy also contains our policies on cookies. NOTE! This privacy and cookies policy only applies to this Website and not to the companies, individuals, organisations or other websites and third-party tools to which there are links to.

This privacy policy document for Passion4FM, hereby referred to “we”, “us”, “our” or just “the website”, defines what type of information that is collected by us to maintain and provide you with the best user-experience, serve you content that is valuable for you, and finally gather overall user-behavior that will be valuable to improve the website for the future. This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set above and is only applicable to our service and website.

We reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes will become effective and binding after their posting on the Passion4FM.com website. Any changes or modifications will be posted on this page. You agree to regularly review this Privacy Policy for revisions and updates and ensure that you are aware of any changes made. Your continued use of the website will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

##### Disabling And/Or Enabling Cookies

By using and submitting personal information to any of our websites, you signify your assent to Passion4FM’s Online Privacy Policy. If you for any reason should want to opt-out you can disable the use of cookies by modifying the settings on your web browser. 

##### External Links

This Privacy Policy applies to www.Passion4FM.com only, and not to other companies, advertising and/or affiliate partners or websites to which we link. When you click on links to these websites or to any other sites from Passion4FM.com, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply. These third party companies may have its own data collection, practices and policies, which we are not responsible for. We cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of such sites meet our high standards. We recommend you to read the privacy policy of the external website before you submit any personal information to them.

You can read more about the intention of our Privacy Policy below. 

* * *

##### Passion4FM’s Online Privacy Policy Document will provide You the answers to these questions: 

    * What kind of information do we collect?
    * How do we use / store information about you?
    * Do We disclose Any User-information to third parties?
    * Passion4FM Cookies Policy 
      * What are Cookies and How Do We Use These Cookies?

### What Information do We Collect From Our Users?

##### Information Automatically Collected When Browsing the Website

When visiting Passion4FM.com there are two types of information we may gather:

    * A) **Personally identifiable information**
    * B) **Non-personally identifiable information**

A) **Personally identifiable information**  
The Website may collect information about You, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us, either by using fill-in forms, such as register as guest-writer, author or contributor on the Website, subscribe to our newsletter, by entering online tournaments, competitions, giveaways or contacting us by e-mail for support or to provide any feedback you may have. The entered data within the form will not be stored on our webserver for any longer than one month.

The different types of _personally identifiable information_ let us provide Our services to You. Such information may include but is not limited to name, e-mail address, demographics, age, website and other important information to identify you as the User. These pieces of information may vary depending on the circumstances, but is gathered to provide You the Support you require, such as letting us get in touch with You and answer any questions you may have by email. 

Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and are stored on your computer’s hard drive and help Us identify you as the User. You have the choice to modify your browser and thus to accept or reject the cookies used by Passion4FM or any of our third party companies/services. 

Read more about [Passion4FM’s cookies policy](http://passion4fm.com/privacy-policy/#cookies-policy "Passion for Football Manager Cookie Policy") here. 

**The personal identifiable information will not be displayed to us when simply browsing the website.**

_Do note that we will get information about your internet protocol (IP) automatically when submitting a form or using our author login page. This information will not be stored for longer than a month. This is done merely to protect us from unprofessional people who wish to spam us or tries to hack the Website._

B) **Non-personally identifiable information**  
This website uses various web analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) and other measurement tools to help analyse how users use the site. The Log files, which we will automatically gather for every visit is pieces of ‘anonymous’ information about the website activity, including how many “hits” a particular web page is getting or how you found the particular page: search term or referring URL. It lets us gather statistics about general user habits and maintain website security. Log files will be used internally only, for internal marketing studies to improve our services, and may be combined with data collected via cookies to help us aggregate behavior patterns of registered users. 

These tools use ‘cookies’, which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for passion4fm.com.

When you visit our website the information gathered within the log files will contain basic information about your behavior, your technology and demographics. In short we will gather _non-personally identifiable information_ about Users, such as Your; 

    * IP address
    * Web browser Information (Google Chrome, Firefox, Linux or other OS
    * Internet Service provider (ISP)
    * Country of origin / language
    * Date and time for visit(s) for analyzing misbehavior or abuse – but we are not to see personal information apart from IP address
    * Referral URL’s
    * Visited pages, number of clicks / referring and exit pages to analyze trends

**We will never (and will not allow any third party) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our site. The Web Analytics vendors do not associate your IP address with any other data held by them. Neither we nor the Web Analytics Vendors will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source, unless you explicity submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.**

##### Social Media Interaction

Passion4FM gives you the option to interact with us through social medias such as Facebook, Twitter, Googleplus, Youtube or Twitch, or through third-party social networking sites, applications or plugins. 

When you engage with our content on or through third-party social networking sites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., Username, photo, gender, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application.

When you provide information from your social media account, it can help enable Us to contact you through the social networking sites. By doing so, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. When you provide personal information to Passion4FM through Our website(s) or on social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.

Through some social networking sites’ privacy settings, you can control what data you share. For more information about how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use. 

* * *

### How Does Passion4FM Use / Store The Information About You? 

Information that we collect for a particular purpose is used for that purpose only. Personally identifiable information will only be used to give you a response to your inquiry. Information gathered from those who register on our website(s) as authors or guest writers is used to provide them with the benefits that come along with registration, such as informational e-mails, author resources and guidelines – where the sole purpose is to provide valuable information or communicate with our authors.

Your personal information will not be distributed to any third-party accossiations for any purpose.

The non-personally identifiable information we collect is gathered solely in the purpose to get records of Your visit and be able to improve the Website with more articles You and other Visitors favor. We do not store any information about your visit other than to analyze and optimize the website content and further improve the reading experience through the use of cookies. These cookies and log files is only stored while browsing the website and session will end when leaving the site. 

In addition, personal and/or demographic information collected through one of the activities set above may be used for our internal marketing studies, so we can constantly improve the services we provide and better meet your standard and needs. 

No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate objectives. 

##### HOW CAN I ACCESS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

If you wish to view, correct, or delete the personal information collected about you, or you wish to subscribe or cancel your subscription to our email newsletters or register / un-register as author / contributor, you can easily do so online. To modify your author account information, log in using your current username and password, select the areas you wish to change, and edit or delete your information. The information you delete online will be immediately removed from our database. If you are experiencing problems with changing your information online, you may contact us at with the email address below. 

##### Passion4FM’s Policy Regarding Children Under 13

We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information such as name and email address from children under 13. Everything published on the website(s) allows all users (including children under 13) to disclose a limited amount of personal information without first telling us their age or parental permission. Such portions of our sites operate activities or provide services in a way that does not require prior parental consent. We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children’s use of online activities regularly.

### Does Passion4FM disclose Any User-information to third parties?

No, Passion4FM do not share any user-information to third party companies or services which you haven’t agreed upon. **All personal information collected is treated as strictly confidential** , but We may disclose User’s personal information if required by law, including but not limited to, disclosure to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with an intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability. 

* * *

## Passion4FM Cookies Policy

### What Are Cookies & How Does Passion4FM Use These Cookies?

Our Website uses cookies to gather personally identifiable information to distinguish You from other visitors. Cookies are a kind of short term memory for the web – a small text file, which are stored in your browser (if accepted by the User) and is sent to Your computer or mobile device by the webserver so that the Website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website. 

The cookies will collect information regarding your use of our Website, information about your device such as the device’s technology, your demographic data and, if you arrived at our website from a referring link, the URL of the linking page. It enables the website to ‘remember’ little bits of information between pages or visits, such as your actions and preferences (such as login preferences, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. The collected data allows us to improve the Website in the future.

The cookies we use are “functional” and “analytical” cookies. The functional cookies are needed to make the site work. The analytical cookies allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they are using it. These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. We use Google Analytics to provide this service, which uses four first party cookies. The data collected is not shared with any other party.

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them in the table below. Please note that this table does not represent a definitive list of the cookies we use and is subject to change. You are therefore advised to check this policy regularly.

**You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.**

##### How to Control, Delete or Manage Cookies

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work. If you have used a Do Not Track browser setting, we take this as a sign that you do not want to allow “analytical” cookies to be set, and they will be blocked by default, which makes sure your visit in our statistics will not be included.

To turn off the use of cookies at anytime, manage them or allow some control over them, please change your specific browser settings under Privacy. You can read more about [how to enable/disable cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/) in this great tutorial. If you like to read more about how cookies work or what cookies are, please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

##### Cookies and Third Parties

Some of the third parties we do use, may use cookies and web beacons. The third parties includes, but are not restricted to Google Analytics and Google Adsense. We may occasionally, with the highest discretion include or offer third party products or services. 

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes when you have not opted into receiving such third party offers and/or newsletters through the website. These third parties will automatically receive your IP address. The advertising networks and ad-servers will use technology on advertises and links on our website to measure effectiveness and personalize the advertising content for better user experience. 

Passion4FM has no access to or control over the use of cookies and storage of personal information created by third party services or websites. If you decide to click on advertises or third party logos displayed on our website, which links to a different website, our privacy policy will no longer apply. You must then read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

**More about Third-Party advertisements**

We also use third party cookies and web beacons in order to support our website through displaying advertisements from our affiliate partners and Google. Third party vendors, including Google Adsense, uses cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

**Doubleclick Cookies**

Google’s use of the [DoubleClick cookie](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/) enables it and its partners to serve ads to you, based on your previously browsing history, and target ads which is of your personal interest, by placing a cookie on your computer. This cookie will not track personal information about You (your name, email address, street address, phone number, passwords or credit card number. 

You can read more about the [DoubleClick cookie used by Google Adsense program](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090) here. 

**How to Disable Ads-serving cookies**

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.) Deleting the doubleclick cookie does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program as a new cookie will be added. You can however disallow cookies by settings, the next time you visit a site running the ads. 

Cookie | Name | Purpose  
---|---|---  
Google Analytics | _utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz |  These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. 

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.   
  
Doubleclick | _drt_  
id |   
Disqus |  | Third Party cookie attached to the ability to leave comments on our website.   
Youtube Cookies (3rd Party) |  | We embed videos from our official YouTube channel using YouTube’s privacy-enhanced mode. This mode may set cookies on your computer once you click on the YouTube video player, but YouTube will not store personally-identifiable cookie information for playbacks of embedded videos using the privacy-enhanced mode.  
Read more at [YouTube’s embedding videos information page](https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/171780?hl=en-GB "Youtube Video embed").   
|  |   
  
PASSION4FM COOKIES POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED 09. SEPTEMBER 2015

_  
If you have any questions or like to report an incident of abuse, please[contact us by email](http://www.passion4fm.com/contact-us/).  
_

* * *
